Hello friends welcome back to my channel so
friends today we will talk
about promo application yes friends the
way the notification is visible, as
soon as you put it on play store this sadak
application will open in front of you this is the
official application of gang to download this application
you have to check the rating here
and you have to download this application by the
way
I have given the link to download the application
in the description you do
not need to go anywhere in the description
now as you check it you will get it there to
download this application
now you talk here what this
gang application gives you and
what does this application
give you on referring so let's talk about it, if you do not refer the
application gives you ₹500 it will remain above you
can see it remains at ₹500
and what does your friend get, your
friend gets a gift of rs.250
this application is giving ₹500 just on referring
you must have heard the name bank caste and lineage
card but those applications do
not give any money for referring but here  The
promo is giving you ₹500 for referring and
your friend is also being given the dance here, it is a
very good thing that the application is
also paying for promoting it, so
hurry up, there is a link in the description,
click on that link and you
can earn ₹500 here for each of your
friends. I will talk about
what work you will have to do here and
how you can earn ₹500. Friends,
after joining the application, you have to
sell any one product.
You have to sell any one product successfully, only then
you will get ₹500 here.
Your friends, the rest of your friend will also
get it in this form when he sells any one
product. This is the biggest thing
here, there are terms and conditions,
you have to understand this. I have received a lot of comments
that we have joined but still we have
not received the drive, that you have got ₹500,
no, this will never happen because its
terms and conditions are that you joined this application
and you get the product.  You have to
select this product here, if it is sold then it gets credited
to your account here
and you also get ₹500 here,
so this promo is the best, it is much better than the
applications that have come till now, like the one I will talk about, this is a very
good promo,
you can use this and easily you can
earn from 50 to 1 lakh rupees monthly here by
inviting your friends and
taking their commission, so friend download it today,
I have given the link in the description,
you do not need to go anywhere, if
you need any support you will
find our number in the description, you can
call me, you will be helped completely here, so
friend I hope
you liked my video, understood it
and if you have
any query related to this then you should contact us immediately,
you will be fully supported and
if you join us then you will get live
time support from here, you will get help, you can
contact us at any time in any condition, you will be fully supported here, so
friends I hope
you liked our video  If you
liked the video then do like it and
share it with your friends and if
you are new to the channel then do subscribe to the channel
so that you get to know about our upcoming videos
first. Friends, we will meet you
in the next video with the next update, till then
bye A
[Music] It has happened
in Hindi.